我已经在华盛顿待了很长时间了
Now, I have been in Washington a long time
我以为我什么都见过了
and I thought I had seen everything,
但是奥布莱恩参议员表现出来的泠漠
but the insensitivity shown by Senator O'Brien
很明显说明
clearly demonstrates that this
这个男人并不拥有判断力与尊严...
man does not possess the judgment and dignity...
真理啊
True statesman right there.
好的吧 我现在需要一个安静的地方来思考
Okay, so now what I need is a quiet place to think
这地方不能有迈克那张蠢脸
that doesn't have Mike's stupid face in it.
我转身 女士
I can turn around, ma'am.
四楼有个小教堂
There's a chapel on the fourth floor.
大家字幕组四楼有个小教堂
EVERYONE There's a chapel on the fourth floor.
大家字幕组
EVERYONE
可以订给您使用大家字幕组
We can make sure it's cleared out for you. EVERYONE
大家字幕组可以订给您使用
EVERYONE We can make sure it's cleared out for you.
大家字幕组
EVERYONE
好 棒大家字幕组
Okay, yeah. EVERYONE
大家字幕组
EVERYONE
- 女士? - 怎么?大家字幕组
- Ma'am? - What? EVERYONE
大家字幕组
EVERYONE
我们所爱的永不逝去大家字幕组
Those we have loved cannot be lost EVERYONE